Nigel Moyes

UX Design and Content Strategy

nigelmoyes.work

<u>nigelcmoyes@gmail.com</u>

in <u>nigel-moyes</u>

awards

2019

'Decisiveness' Award

Tundra Team Awards

2018

'Care' Award

Tundra Team Awards

2016

Digital Team of the Year

ADMA IQ Awards

2015

'Rookie of the year'

Movember Foundation

skills

Wireframing and prototyping

User personas, journeys and flows

Information architecture

Workshop facilitation

Presentations and stakeholder engagement

Content strategy

UX copy and copywriting

Front-end development

Visual design

about

I'm a passionate, dilligent and committed User Experience and Content Strategy expert, with a knack for people and problem solving. I'm ready for my next challenge in UX and would love to talk about how I can help you and your users.

work experience

Tundra

2019 - Present

Strategy Director (Acting)

Directing and overseeing the team's UX, content and strategy approaches. Providing training and mentorship. Developing close relationships with

clients to unearth new possibilities.

Tundra

2018 - 2019

UX and Content Strategist

Part of a small, high-performing multi disciplinary team, leading content and UX activities across a

number of large clients.

Deakin

2016 - 2018

Content Strategist / Writer

Content strategist and copywriter for Deakin's public

website redevelopment project, a massive and

multi-year replatforming effort.

Movember Foundation

2014 - 2016

Content Coordinator

Responsible for the coordination and implementation

of content from global teams across multiple

timezones, for use on 23 websites and 2 mobile apps.

tools

#Figma #AxureRP #Framer #Protopie #Photoshop #Mural #Miro #Optimal Workshop #HTML #CSS #JS + jQuery #Notion #VScode Bachelor of Communications

education

Swinburne Online

HTML, CSS and Javascript

SuperHi

User Experience Design

SuperHi

Visual Design

SuperHi